The Man Who Cried is a romance, drama, music film directed by Sally Potter.
A young refugee travels from Russia to America in search of her
lost father and falls in love with a gypsy horseman.
Suzie, played by Christina Ricci.
Cesar, played by Johnny Depp.
Lola, played by Cate Blanchett.
Dante Dominio, played by John Turturro.
Felix Perlman, played by Harry Dean Stanton.
Father, played by Oleg Yankovskiy.
The Man Who Cried is a 2000 drama film written and directed by Sally Potter, and starring
Christina Ricci, Cate Blanchett, Johnny Depp, Harry Dean Stanton and John Turturro.
The film tells the story of a young Jewish girl who, after being separated from her father in Soviet Russia, grows
up in England and moves to Paris as a young adult, shortly before the beginning of World War II.
It is the last film worked on by the French cinematographer Sacha Vierny.
The film explores themes of dancing, france, england, gypsy, singer.
The tone is emotional.